{
    "mode": 0,
    "quiz_id": "632b0d49ec45f04d9b7e44ce",
    "quizContent": {
        "Subject": "ITEL 316 - Prelim Reviewer",
        "quizName": "ITEL 316 - Prelim Reviewer",
        "questions": [
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 6.0",
                "answers": ["23"],
                "choices": ["20","21","22","23"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 5.1",
                "answers": ["22"],
                "choices": ["20","21","22","23"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 5.0",
                "answers": ["21"],
                "choices": ["20","21","22","23"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 4.4W",
                "answers": ["20"],
                "choices": ["20","21","22","23"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 4.4",
                "answers": ["19"],
                "choices": ["16","17","18","19"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 4.3",
                "answers": ["18"],
                "choices": ["16","17","18","19"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 4.2 to 4.2.2",
                "answers": ["17"],
                "choices": ["16","17","18","19"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 4.1 to 4.1.1",
                "answers": ["16"],
                "choices": ["16","17","18","19"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 4.0.3 to 4.0.4",
                "answers": ["15"],
                "choices": ["13","14","15","16"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 4.0 to 4.0.2",
                "answers": ["14"],
                "choices": ["13","14","15","16"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 3.2",
                "answers": ["13"],
                "choices": ["11","12","13","14"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 3.1.x",
                "answers": ["12"],
                "choices": ["10","11","12","13"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 3.0.x",
                "answers": ["11"],
                "choices": ["10","11","12","13"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 2.3.3 to 2.3.4",
                "answers": ["10"],
                "choices": ["10","11","12","13"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 2.3 to 2.3.2",
                "answers": ["9"],
                "choices": ["6","7","8","9"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 2.2.x",
                "answers": ["8"],
                "choices": ["5","6","7","8"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 2.1.x",
                "answers": ["7"],
                "choices": ["5","6","7","8"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 2.0.1",
                "answers": ["6"],
                "choices": ["5","6","7","8"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 2.0",
                "answers": ["5"],
                "choices": ["5","6","7","8"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 1.6",
                "answers": ["4"],
                "choices": ["1","2","3","4"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 1.5",
                "answers": ["3"],
                "choices": ["1","2","3","4"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 1.1",
                "answers": ["2"],
                "choices": ["1","2","3","4"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "API level of android 1.0",
                "answers": ["1"],
                "choices": ["1","2","3","4"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "It is an integer value that uniquely identifies the framework API version offered by an android version.",
                "answers": ["API Level"],
                "choices": ["Integer level", "Open Source Level", "Access Level", "API Level"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "Android 1.0 was released in ____ 2008",
                "answers": ["September"],
                "choices": ["August", "September", "November", "December"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "What year the 1st android SDK was released?",
                "answers": ["2007"],
                "choices": ["2006", "2007", "2008", "2009"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "Android was developed by ______ led by Google, and other companies",
                "answers": [],
                "choices": ["Microsoft", "Open Source Community", "Linus", "Open Handset Alliance"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "Android is an _____ operating system",
                "answers": ["Linux-based"],
                "choices": ["MacOs-based", "Windows-based", "Linux-based"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "It is a general abstraction for something that can be drawn",
                "answers": ["Drawable"],
                "choices": ["Video", "Image", "Drawable", "Animation"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "You can use the _____ class and its subclasses to draw shapes and images.",
                "answers": ["Drawable"],
                "choices": ["Java","Drawable", "Animation"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "Most of Android UI is defined in ____ files",
                "answers": ["XML"],
                "choices": ["Java Class", "XML"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "The user interface of an Android application is built using _____.",
                "answers": ["Views"],
                "choices": ["Intent","XML","Activity","Views"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "Intent sendIntent = new Intent(getApplicationContext(), ActivityTwo.class); startActivity(______);",
                "answers": ["sendIntent"],
                "choices": ["new Intent","this.Intent","sendIntent","ActivityTwo.class"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "Android system initiates code in an Activity instance by invoking specific callback methods",
                "answers": ["True"],
                "choices": ["True", "False"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "In android, app/program are launched with a main() method",
                "answers": ["False"],
                "choices": ["True", "False"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "It is a crucial component of an Android app",
                "answers": ["Activity class", "Activity"],
                "choices": ["Activity class", "Intent", "XML", "Java"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "Each application window is called an activity and they can be called using ____",
                "answers": ["Intent", "Intents"],
                "choices": ["Intent", "Activity", "TextView", "EmptyActivity"]
            },{
                "type": 0,
                "question": "Android, we can only put one application in focus at a time",
                "answers": ["True"],
                "choices": ["True", "False"]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "Android OS had only been used since ____",
                "answers": [
                    "2003"
                ],
                "choices": [
                    "2008",
                    "2003",
                    "2005",
                    "2006"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "Who owns android?",
                "answers": [
                    "Google"
                ],
                "choices": [
                    "Google",
                    "Microsoft",
                    "Amazon",
                    "Apple"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "What component is used to display text?",
                "answers": [
                    "TextView"
                ],
                "choices": [
                    "Intent",
                    "ImageView",
                    "Button",
                    "TextView"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": 0,
                "question": "What programming language is used in android?",
                "answers": [
                    "Java"
                ],
                "choices": [
                    "Cobol",
                    "C",
                    "Java",
                    "Rust"
                ]
            }
        ],
        "answeredBy": []
    }
}